<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on maxfieldlehman.com</title>
    <link>https://maxfieldlehman.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on maxfieldlehman.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 12:33:45 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://maxfieldlehman.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Serving This Site</title>
      <link>https://maxfieldlehman.com/posts/serving-this-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 12:33:45 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maxfieldlehman.com/posts/serving-this-site/</guid>
      <description>Somewhat predictably, the first thing I took care on here after making that &#34;plans going forward&#34; list was not even featured on said list: setting up HTTPS.
To be honest, I&#39;m 100% faking it at the moment, but seeing as it&#39;s a static site that doesn&#39;t handle anything critical, I really just wanted people to be subtly reassured by the little lock in the address bar.
I set up &#34;flexible&#34; HTTPS (including redirects from bare HTTP URLs) and caching with a free-tier Cloudflare account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building This Site</title>
      <link>https://maxfieldlehman.com/posts/building-this-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 22:27:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maxfieldlehman.com/posts/building-this-site/</guid>
      <description>I shopped around a little before deciding to use Hugo as the generator for my site. I&#39;d been meaning to give Gutenberg a chance for a while, and Hakyll appeals to the part of my brain that likes taking painfully abstract math courses, but in the end I decided to go for something a bit more established and popular.
One of the perks of Hugo is Org mode support as a drop in replacement for Markdown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genesis</title>
      <link>https://maxfieldlehman.com/posts/genesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 14:15:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maxfieldlehman.com/posts/genesis/</guid>
      <description>At a truly inopportune time, I&#39;ve decided to finally get this site going again. I&#39;m already spending too much time tinkering with personal projects instead of class assignments, but at least with this I&#39;ll have something I made to point to.
This site used to be up as a sort of mini-resume, but I let it slide into obselesence and killed it rather than leave an inaccurate site up without the time or motivation to maintain it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>